Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat. N.
Hey,
Good morning and welcome to Movement Church. Are you ready to worship
the Lord this morning? All right, come on. Put your hands together.
Who's got joy in this place? >> All right, here we go.
[music]
[music] There's a song in my spirit. There's a joy in my
soul. What a way [singing] I'll worship [music] anyway.
Only the devil [music and singing] can try it. Try to quiet this song,
but I'll sing out even louder [singing and music] than before.
I'm going to [music and singing] lift my voice and sing. I'm going to
give him everything. I'm going [singing] to shout till these walls come
down. [music] I see the [singing] light in Jesus name. I'm going
to laugh my fears away. I'm going [music and singing] to dance till these
walls come down.
[music]
There's a song in my spirit. There's a joy in my soul.
Come what will come what may I worship anyway. [music]
Oh the devil [singing] can try it. Try to quiet the [music]
song but I'll sing out even louder than before.
I'm [music and singing] going to lift my voice and sing. I'm going to
give him everything. I'm going [music and singing] to shout till these walls come
down.
I see the light in [music and singing] Jesus name. I'm going to laugh
my fears away. [music] I'm going [singing] to dance till these walls
go down.
Oh, we thank you for your [music]
[singing] let's declare [music] this today. Say the spirit of [singing] joy
breaking out. We can feel it all [music] around. How we walked
in [singing] won't be how we're leaving. [music]
[singing] >> He is doing something new. And we know that [music and singing] he's
not through. It's the name of Jesus. We believe you. >> Oh, spirit
of joy. >> Spirit [music and singing] of joy breaking out. We feel it all
around. [music] how we walked [singing] in behind.
[music and singing]
[singing] [music]
I'm going to shout till these walls [singing] go down. [music] Oh,
when I see the light in Jesus name, I'm going to laugh
[singing and music] my fears away. I'm going to dance till these walls [singing]
go down.
I'm [music] going to dance till these walls go down. [singing] I'm
going to [music] dance till these walls go down. praise in this
place. [music] Hallelujah. Oh, we bless your [singing] name, Jesus.
>> Come on. Do we have a praise in the house of the
Lord this morning? [music] I've got [singing] a praise that will break
off any chains. I've got a song [music] that makes hell begin
[singing] to shake. I've got a shout that breaks [music] their man
from their graves. Going to let it out. Going to let it
out. Going to let it out.
We [music] worship you.
Why would I ever [music] stay silent when you are the one
[singing] who told me to speak? But how could [music] I ever
be quiet when your spirit's in this authority? [music and singing] I'm not ashamed.
I won't be [music] afraid. You got to let [singing] it out.
I've got a praise that will break off any chains. I've got
a song [music and singing] that makes hell begin to shake. I've got a
shout that brings [music and singing] their men from their let it out. Go
let it out. [music] Let it out. [singing]
Why [music and singing] would I need men's permission when you're calling me [singing]
to live wild and free? Why [music] would I need man's religion
when your spirit's [music] living inside of me? I'm not ashamed. I
won't [singing] be afraid. Going to let it [music] out. I've got
a praise that will break [singing] off heavy chains. I've got a
[music] song that they tell me to say. I've got a [singing]
shout that brings them from let it [music and singing] out. Let it out.
It's like a fire that [music] shut up in my bones. It's
like a passion that's burning in my soul. It's running wild [music and singing]
and I'm losing all control. Let it out. Let [music] it out.
>> [singing]
[music]
>> Oh, [singing] I'm going to sing till I [music] have no voice.
Even then, I'm going to make some [singing] noise. I [music] don't
care what people say. [singing] Cuz I'm going to praise you anyway.
I'm going [music and singing] to sing till I have no voice. Even then,
I'm going to make some noise. I don't [music and singing] care what people
say cuz I'm going to praise you [music and singing] anyway. I'm going to
sing till I have no voice. Even then, I'm going to make
[singing and music] some noise. I don't care what people say. I'm going to
praise [music] you anyway. I've got a praise that will break off
[music and singing] heavy chains. I've got a song that makes hell begin to
shake. [singing] I've got a shout that brings dead men from their
[music] gra. Let it out. Let it out. It's like a fire
that shut up in my bones. It's like a passion [music] that's
[singing] burning in my soul. It's running wild and I'm losing all
[music and singing] control. Going to let it out. Going to let it out.
Going to let it out. [music and singing] Yeah, we worship you.
Oh, come on. Let praise unto the Lord in this place. Hallelujah.
Oh, we bless your name, Jesus. Oh, we bless your name, Jesus.
[music and singing] He's such a good and a faithful God. Amen. >> Let's lift
our hands and let's just [music] worship him in this place. Oh,
we thank you Lord.
Oh, we bless your name Jesus.
You are [music and singing] so good, so faithful God.
You're my strength. Though the [singing] earth pass away the new
remains
and it is written that you provide [singing] every need everywhere
that you [music] lead.
For you keep your [singing and music] promises,
your [music and singing] goodness never ends. From [music and singing] generation
to generation, [singing] [music] you keep your covenant.
Oh, we see [music and singing] your faithfulness
from [singing and music] generation
to generation.
[singing]
It is written,
we're redeemed [music] by your [singing] blood. All the old has passed
away. The new has come. For it is written,
it's not by [singing and music] power or might, but by the spirit of
the [singing] living God in love.
You keep your [music and singing] promise. >> Your goodness never ends. >> Your goodness
never [music] ends. [singing] generations from generation
to [music and singing] generation
and you keep your covenant. I [singing] see your faithfulness [music]
[singing] for generation [music] from generation
to generation. [singing]
Oh, come on. Just lift your [music] hands and thank [singing] the
Lord. He's a faithful God. Oh, we thank you, Jesus. Oh, we
[music and singing] thank you, Lord.
We will [music] trust you and believe.
Let [music and singing] it be. You alone will be a fine foundation. [music and singing]
And what you spokeen is enough. And it's the crown [singing] we're
standing on. You are God. And we [music] will not be shen.
Oh, [music] we will trust you and [singing] believe. As it's written,
let it [music] be. Cuz you alone [singing] will be a firm
foundation.
>> What [music] is enough is a crown we're [singing] standing on. You
are God [music] and we will not [singing] be shen. [music]
You keep [music] your promises [singing]
never [music] end. Your goodness is never [music] >> from generation
>> from generation
to generation. [music]
And you keep your cup [singing] for your faithfulness.
[music] [singing] Faithfulness generation. [music] From generation to
generation [singing] to generation generation [music] generation
to generation [music] generation >> generation
to gener
>> [music] >> Oh, we thank you for your faithful name. Oh, we thank
you.
Hey.
Come on, lift your hands and just worship him this morning. We
thank you, Lord. He's a faithful [music] God. Oh, we worship you,
Jesus.
We worship you Lord.
Thank you Lord.
What has [singing] washed away [music] my s?
Nothing [music and singing] but the blood of Jesus [music] and
what has [singing] made me whole again.
Nothing [singing] [music] but the blood of Jesus. [singing]
>> [music]
>> Oh, and [singing] what has [music] washed away my [singing] sin?
Nothing but the [music] blood of [singing] Jesus.
And what [music] has made me whole [singing] again? [music]
Nothing but the blood of Jes. [music] [singing]
[music]
[singing]
Nothing [music] but the blood of Jesus. [singing and music]
has made me whole again. [music and singing] We sing nothing
but the light of Jesus. [music] [singing] And
[music] preious is [singing] the love [music] that
makes me [music] white [singing] as snow.
[singing] I [music] know nothing but [singing] the blood
of Jesus. [music] Operation
precious is [music and singing] thous
[music] [singing]
[singing] [music]
[singing] of [music] Jesus.
Thank you for your love.
[music and singing] Thank you for your love.
[music]
>> [singing]
[music] >> Oh, I thank you.
Oh, precious. [music] Preious [singing] is
[music] the love that makes me [music] white
as [singing] snow.
>> [music and singing] >> bound
[music] nothing but the [singing] blood of Jesus.
And how [music] [singing] precious is the blood
[music] that [singing] makes me white as [music and singing] snow. Oh
no other [music] found [singing]
nothing [music] but the blood of [singing] Jesus.
[singing]
Oh nothing but the blood [music] Jesus. Oh, come on [singing] church.
We thank you for his love. [music]
We thank you [singing] for
your love. >> Thank you for your [music]
[singing] sing. So precious and [music] preious
is [singing] the glow that makes me [music]
white as [singing] snow. [music]
I know nothing [singing] but the blood of [music] Jesus.
[singing]
>> There's nothing but the blood. [music and singing] >> There's nothing but the blood
for those [music] who worship you. We [singing] thank you. We praise
you, Lord.
>> We thank you for your
love. Thank you. [music] Thank you, [singing] Lord. Thank you, Lord. Come
on, church. One more time, let's just lift our hands and [music]
say thank you. >> Oh, he [singing] really came [music]
for us. So we [music and singing] say thank you Lord. We say
[music and singing] thank you. We say thank [music] you.
We [singing and music] say thank you.
Say [singing] thank you.
Thank you Jesus.
>> Thank you Jesus [music and singing] for
Jesus. Just stay in this position of worship, this place of worship.
Tap into the presence of God.
>> We thank you, Lord. We acknowledge your presence today. We say yes
to you today. We move with you today, Holy Spirit.
Thank you, Lord. We thank you, Lord.
You know, we serve a God who is [music] the same yesterday,
today, and forever. >> And I [music] love singing about this because and
it's and I think for some people when you're new to this,
it's like, man, why are we singing about blood? This is kind
of strange. But see, the blood of Jesus bought and paid for
us to be free, to be washed clean. You know, we're learning
about our covenant with God. And when we sing about the blood,
what we're singing about is what he did for us. The sacrifice
paid for us to redeem us and to set us free. And
where does that come from? What is the purpose of that? Why?
What drove God to that? What drove Jesus to that? I've been
really [music] meditating on the love of God. Because that's that's the
driving force behind the sacrifice [music] of Jesus. The love of God.
And see, you can grow up, especially if you grow up in
the church and you hear about the love of God and you
sing Jesus loves me, this I know and it be it can
become too familiar and [music] start being head knowledge instead of revelation
knowledge. And when the love of God is revelation knowledge to us,
there is something that it it does in you. There is a
boldness that [music] it creates in you. I want to read this
passage in first John chapter [music] 4 and verse 9. It says,
"In this was manifested the love of God [music] toward us, because
that God sent his only begotten son into the world that we
might live through him. Herein is love, not that we loved God,
but that he loved us and sent his son to be the
perpetuation for our sins." I love that passage. is not about you
loving God. That happens as a byproduct of a revelation of the
fact that he loves us. He loves you in your mess, in
your imperfection, in your shortcomings, in all the places that you He
knows you fully and loves you. How many of us can really
say we have anybody else in this life that really loves us
like that? I mean, it's a it's a blessing if you've experienced
that kind of love. But it's rare for somebody to fully know
you, everything about you, every hidden thing, and to love you completely
and not just love you, but do something with that. Send his
son to die for you. Guys, if you could get a revelation
of this, see what I've been studying out is love is the
foundation for all of the the things that we walk in. How
can we be healed? Because he loves us. How can we prosper?
Because he loves us. How can we be free from anxiety, depression,
fear, all the things that plague us? Because he loves us. And
so what we do when those things come at us, we say,
"Who do you think you are? I am the beloved of God.
What right do you have to touch me? You have no right.
You know, I think about it like this. Okay, mamas, you can
relate to this. I'm sure daddies can too, but you know, there
is something that comes out in you when somebody comes after your
kids. They call it a mama bear, right? Someone comes after your
kids. There is something that comes out of you. Sometimes it's not
pretty, but you want to you want to protect your child, right?
and you're going to do what's necessary to protect your child. How
much more does our God love you, his child, that if the
enemy is after you, you need to just stand up and say,
"You know what? He's my God. What do you think you're doing?
You have no right to me." And then we stand in the
love of God. See, that's the healing isn't about works. It's not
about attaining this. It's not about performance. It's about recognizing [music] who
loves you and what belongs to you as a result of the
love. Amen. >> I want to pray over you. Father, I just declare
right now. [music] And I pray that every single person in here
will see evidence of your love for [music] them right now, all
day long, today, all week long. Father, that you will reveal your
[music] immense, great, immeasurable, unending, unconditional love for them. that
they will see it and know that they are loved without fail,
without any kind of condition, no matter who who how they behave, no matter
what they do. God, that you love them. I thank [music] you,
Father, for a re a revealing of this love. And Father, I
pray that we as carriers [music] of that love will bring that
revelation to others in the way that we love them. and we
will be a vessel [music] of your love for others. I thank
you for that, God. I thank you for giving us revelation within
our hearts that would completely transform the way we live our lives.
We love [music] you and we praise you. In Jesus name we
pray. Amen. Amen. You [music] guys can be seated.
Well, good morning and welcome to Movement Church. I don't know about
you, but there is no place I'd rather be on a Monday,
a Sunday [music] morning. Monday morning, too. Sunday morning. I love coming
to church. Uh we had to miss [music] last week and it
was like I didn't know what to do with myself being out
one week. We don't like missing. I want to be here every
Sunday. This is the greatest [music] group of people I know. Amen.
Well, if this is your first time, uh we want to welcome
you. We want to say thank you for coming. We want to
say that we are so glad that you are here and we
would love to invite you to fill out a connection card. [music]
Uh you can do that by scanning the QR code on the
screen in front of you. Um you can do that by tapping
the little circles on the seat back in front of you. It'll
take you to [music] a place where you can fill that out.
Um we also want to invite you to pick up a welcome
packet. If this is your first time, we want to just say
welcome. [music] We want to give you a little information about the
church. Um there's a message in here from our pastors [music] and
there's a gift card to Summer Moon. I mean, who doesn't want
that, right? So, if you if this is your first time or
if you've been before, [music] but you haven't picked one of these
up, be sure you do that before you leave today. Uh we
would love to bless you and just say thank you for being
here. Um every week we say our confessions. Uh you know, the
the vision of this church is moving people from where they are
to where God is [music] calling them to be. Okay? It's life,
freedom, and fulfillment. It's helping you [music] to find life through Jesus,
the only one that can lead us into true life. And upon
following him, you walk in freedom from anything that's ever held you
back in life. And then as you walk in that freedom, then
you will live in what it looks like to truly be fulfilled.
I have never been [music] more fulfilled in my entire life than
in what I am doing today. Never. [music] And it just keeps
getting better. life with the Lord. When you're walking closely to him
and you're growing and you're learning [music] about him more, it just
gets better. That's the will of God anyways. So, if [music] you're
not seeing that in your life, I want to invite you to
get connected here. Start serving [music] here because when you begin to
serve and you begin to submit yourself humbly to the Lord, you
will begin to do things that you never thought you could do.
And in that you will see that growth and that [music] transformation.
With this though, with this growth, this church begins to grow. We've
got more people. It's full every week, right? We need more space.
And we don't we talk about this because we keep the vision
in front of us every week. You know, the Bible tells us
to do that. [music] And we are growing. We're getting land. We're
building buildings. The school right now is pre-K through [music] third grade
at second grade this year. And we'll be growing all the way
up through 12th. 12th grade. Well, if you walk around this building
at all, that don't fit here. But that's the calling of God.
So, the calling of God is to build a school pre-K through
12th grade. Well, if that's the calling of God, that means he's
got something more to fulfill that. And so, we say every week
these confessions so that we don't forget this is where we're [music]
going. This isn't where we're staying. We are moving from here. So,
I want to invite you uh to say these [music] with us
by faith, believing in where God is calling our church. All grace
abounds towards us. We have everything we [music] need to accomplish all
that God has called us to do. We thank you Lord for
the provision to build all the buildings needed for Movement Church, [music]
Movement Christian Academy, Movement Bible College, and every work you call us
to do. We say yes to your [music] plan, and we thank
you for your grace to complete our assignment. We call this done
[music] in Jesus' name. Amen. Amen. Well, as we prepared to receive
[music] our tithes and offering, I want to read a passage to
you. There was a story that I was reading and man, it
got me fired [music] up. So, every week, I am so thankful
for a pastor uh that desires [music] to teach us what the
word says about everything. and especially with finances. I have learned so
much in this [music] area and grown so much in this area
and we've seen such fruit in this area. And so it's so
exciting to me [music] um when I get to share this because
I believe there is so much power in knowing the truth behind
God's will for [music] your finances. Okay? And and like I'm saying,
God is growing us. Well, the way he's [music] going to do
that is through you, through the people of this church sewing into
what God is doing [music] here. So I was reading this story
about Elijah in first kings chapter [music] 17 and Elijah tells Ahab
just to summarize he tells Ahab it's not going to rain the
king you know [music] and that makes someone not very happy when
the prophet says things that are not good for you. So he
flees and God is taking care of him by this [music] river
providing the water and the birds are bringing him food. Well the
river dries up because there's no rain, right? And so God's going
to move him somewhere else because [music] when God tells you to
do something and you're obedient, you can trust he's going to provide
for you every time. So in [music] in chapter 17:9, he gives
these instructions to Elijah and he says, "Arise, get thee to Zerapath,
which belongs to Zidon, and dwell there. Behold, I have commanded a
widow woman there to sustain [music] you." So Elijah goes, and when
he gets there, he sees this woman. and she's picking [music] up
sticks. And I think it's so interesting because it says here he's
commanded her, which means this woman's always already been given some kind
of instructions by the Lord. So when Elijah goes to her, he
says, "Go get me a drink first." And then she's going. And
as she's going, he says, "Also, bring me some bread." And the
woman [music] says, "I don't have any bread. All I have is
a little bit of flour and a little bit of oil. And
I was just about to go take these sticks, make this [music]
for me and my son, and then we're going to die. They've
got nothing. They're starving. What an interesting person for the Lord to
send Elijah to to sustain him. Isn't that interesting? You know, it
would seem logical for God to send Elijah to someone that's wealthy,
who's got a lot of food to sustain him, but that's not
what God does. See, that's not how God does things. I think
so many times we think we need to be the wealthiest person
in the room in order to be able to contribute to the
mission. God used a widow woman who is planning to die because
of she that they have nothing. So then this is the good
the best part. So then Elijah says, "Okay, you go do that.
You go make that, but you feed me first. Feed me first,
then feed you and your son." I mean, talk about taking another
step. Give me every what you have, but don't feed yourself. You're
starving. I get that. But feed me. Oh my goodness. How many
people have heard [music] a message where the where the minister said,
"Take, give me what you got. I know you're starving, but take
care of me first." How many people be like, "Blasy. I'm leaving
this place." I love God because see, when she was obedient to
what the Lord commanded her to do, not only did the Lord
sustain Elijah, but now her flour and oil did not run out
the entire time [music] Elijah was staying with her. the whole time
for years. He was with her for years, two to three years.
And in that time, her son [music] gets sick and he makes
him well. There is benefit when you decide and make up your
mind, Lord, when you command me to give. [music] Whether I have
little, whether I have much, I'm going to be obedient to that.
There is something [music] phenomenally supernatural that will come. I'm telling you,
you can trust God with your finances. So much of the world,
the Christian world today, wants to give when we feel emotional, wants
to give when we feel drawn to a cause, wants to give
because we feel like we've got enough this month. [music] So now
we're going to give. That isn't biblical giving. Biblical giving is I
am committing to obedience to the Lord no matter what it might cost
me. And then when you step out in that, it will cost
you nothing. You're going to be blessed. And and I I read
this quote this week and it says, you know, we don't give
to live. We are not giving to get. We should expect it.
It is a promise, but that isn't the heart behind it. We
are to live to give. Your existence should be to give. And
when you do, then you live abundantly. Guys, God is so cool.
But he needs us to trust him in the least [music] of
these things, which is finances. It's the least. If we can't trust
him in our finances, you're not [music] trusting him in other areas.
And I can tell you that right now. It's the least of
those. I want to encourage you today. If this is an area
that has been a struggle for you, just approach it like this
woman here. God, you've commanded me to give to you, so I'm
doing it today. [music] And I'm just going to trust that you'll
do what you say you would do. Amen. Let's pray. Lord, we
just thank you for your faithfulness that when you say it, it
is done and you will fulfill it, that you perform what you
promise in your word. And I thank you for that today, Father,
[music] that as as the people of this church commit in this
area, God, there will be such a harvest that there will not
be room in this church to contain it. that we'll have so
much giving that we would have to tell people to stop because
it [music] we is way more than what we need. I thank
you, Father, for the provision in that. Thank you that we will
be able to do everything that we are called to do as
a church because of [music] the faithfulness and the trust in you.
We love you, Lord. We surrender everything that we have to you.
In Jesus name [music] we pray. Amen. >> Amen. And boy, that's a
good word, wasn't it? >> That was a good word. Did you Are
you ready to receive from the word today? >> Did you come expecting
today? >> You know, I was uh I was I love what Lindsay
was sharing there because, you know, so many times uh we look
at ourselves and our own ability and what we have, but this
woman didn't have anything. And I find it funny, it's so ironic
how God does things, right? God brought us here to Salana, Texas,
and he brought us here and and we have a church full
of you guys. And you might be looking at your wallet saying,
"I can't afford that. I can't afford that." Well, God's doing it
again. >> I said he's doing it again. >> And you need to start
thinking like this woman was thinking, right? You need to start thinking
like her and be willing to give and do whatever it is
that God calls you to do. Amen. >> And when you do, as
Lindsay was saying, something supernatural happens on the inside of you. Amen.
How many you like the supernatural? >> Amen. Praise God. Well, I got
a quick dad joke for you before we get in the word
today. Y'all love my dad jokes, right? >> Come on now. This is
a really good one. What do you call a deer with no
eyes? >> No idea. Who said that? [laughter]
Oh, the kids get my dad jokes. The kids love my dad
jokes. Here's another one. How many names can also pass as numbers?
I can only think of one. >> One. I can only think of
one. One. You love it. You love that one. I know you
did. Praise God. We're talking in this series about covenant living. How
to live in your covenant. I believe this is one of the
most foundational things that Christians do not know is how to live
in their covenant. Matter of fact, I go so far as to
say this. Most Christians don't know anything about this. Most Christians when
you start talking to them about their covenant with God, they would
probably look at you a little bit strange because they don't know
anything about it. They don't know what it means for them. All
they know is we take communion at church. That's all they know.
You know, I it's funny. I was uh when I was working,
I first started working and I was in college. uh this lady,
we hired this lady to do a job and she worked in
the same area as me and she was doing the side hustle
thing at the same time and she was uh selling these like
these water filtration systems and she was making some flyers up at
work one day when she was going to go out and start
marketing, you know, her little side hustle and start passing these out.
And she showed me a picture of it of this advertisement that
she made and the advertisement says something like this. Are you tired
of having all that chlorine in your water? Are you tired of
tasting chlorine in your water? The problem was she spelled chlorine. C
H L O R I N G. Chlorine.
And I and I laugh, but you know, this was not Chris.
Now, this was like 21 year old Chris. I didn't say a word.
I thought, if you're not smart enough to know how to spell
chlorine, you don't need to be selling water filtration systems. They didn't
know how to spell it. And they had spellch check back then.
Yes, they did have spell check back then. And and so that's
that's how I feel a lot of times about people and their
covenant, how Christians feel about their covenant. They know a few words.
They know a little bit about it, but they don't know really
anything that they're talking about. And so we've been reading here in
our foundational scripture, Ephesians 2:11. He said this, "Therefore remember that you
once Gentiles in the flesh, who are called uncircumcision by what is
called the circumcision, made in the flesh by hands, that at that
time you were without Christ, being aliens from the commonwealth of Israel,
and strangers from the covenants of promise." Say strangers. >> Strangers. >> What does
that mean? That means you're not aware of you're you're not familiar
with the covenants of promise. And look what it says here. When
you're in that situation, look at you. It says, "Being aliens of
the commonwealth of Israel, strangers from the covenants of promises, having no
hope and without God in the world." You know, if you don't
activate your covenant promises, you're without God's help in this world. >> Amen.
If you don't learn how to live in your covenant, you will
live your entire life as a Christian wondering why this is happening.
How many people do you know? How many Christians do you know
are waiting on God to heal them? How many Christians do you
know are waiting on God to pour out financial provision on them?
How many Christians do you know are begging and pleading with God
to do these things in their life? And they that the reason
they're doing that is because they do not know their covenant. They
do not know what belongs to them. They do not know that
Jesus I said Jesus has already done it for you. >> He's
already promised it. >> Now, if I were to promise you something and
then you turn right around and you're begging me to do it,
you know what that tells me? That tells me you don't believe
my word. if I promised it. I said, "I promise, Michelle, I'm
going to buy you a cheeseburger at McDonald's. I promise." She's like, "No,
please don't. No, I promise I'm going I promise you." And then
and then she comes up to me and says, "Pastor, could you
buy me a cheeseburger?" I mean, I I know you said it,
but I could you just tell me again. Could you just I
don't know. I don't know if I can trust what you say. I
don't know if I could go actually go to McDonald's and expect
you to actually hand me that cheeseburger and buy that cheese. I
mean, think about how how that would be against my character and
against my nature. But that's exactly what Christians do to God every
single day. >> You you know, people that are he's talking about people
that don't have Christ in this world being strangers to the covenants
of promise. But there are many Christians today who are strangers to
the covenants of promise and they don't trust God at all >> with
anything. >> Look what it says here in verse number 13. But now
say now. >> Now, >> now in Christ Jesus, you who were once far
off have been brought near by the blood of Christ. >> You're no
longer a stranger to the covenants of promise. You're supposed to learn
something. We're supposed to be growing and learning as Christians. Amen. Well,
pastors, when do you stop growing and learning? That's what I want
to know. When have I arrived? I feel like I've arrived. I
feel like I already know some things. When do I start? I
mean, I've read the Bible all the way through. Me and Jamie,
we've read the Bible all the way through multiple times. I think
I'm there. Do you know what? As you're here on this earth,
you will never arrive. There is no point where you arrive and
suddenly you don't you don't need to keep growing and learning about
your covenant with God. Well, I've heard teaching on this. Well, you're
about to hear some more >> because you need to know your covenant
and and you find out how much you trust in your covenant
with God. When something bad happens in your life, >> you find out
exactly where people are in their belief in their covenant, in their
trust. Well, I don't know if I can trust God's word. Well, I
don't know if God's going to come through for me. and they're worried
and they're afraid and they're full of anxiety. You know, I just
described most people. >> They're worried and they're afraid and they have all
this anxiety because they don't know their covenant. >> They don't know their
God. They don't know he's a covenant keeping God. And if God
said it, >> well, come on, somebody. >> If he said it, it is
a covenant promise. >> That means if he said it, he's going to
do it. That's right. >> Because he said it, right? If you can't
trust his covenant promises, then you don't understand your God. >> We read
this last week. He said, "My covenant I will not break." >> What
do you think? You think he means that? Well, I don't know if
I could trust him. >> I don't know if I could trust him with
my family. I don't know if I could trust him with my finances.
I don't know if I can do that. He said he will
not break his covenant. >> So, when you find a promise in the
word of God, you can stand on that promise. you can believe
what he said >> because his covenant he will not break. >> Amen. >> So,
we're going to dive a little bit deeper here today. Oh man,
we're going to get some good stuff today. >> It's going to be
good. You know, at the beginning of this year, the Lord spoke
a word to me. Y'all remember the the series we taught at
the beginning of this year? The Lord spoke to me and said,
"2026 is a year of new beginnings. >> It's a year of new
beginnings." And we taught a whole series on new beginnings. what a
new beginning is. And uh some of you are probably thinking, you
know, here we are in July. Some of you are probably thinking,
well, when's a new beginning going to start for me? You know,
I haven't seen a new beginning in my 2026 yet. Well, perhaps
you're not standing in your covenant. >> Perhaps we don't know enough about
our covenant promises to be able to step into all that God
has for us in 2026. But let me tell you what, that
ends today. >> Amen. Amen. So, let's read here in Genesis chapter 17.
We're going to start in verse one, and we're going to see
something about our covenant. In Genesis 17:1, it says, "When Abram was
99 years old, the Lord appeared to Abram and said to him,
I am Almighty God. Walk before me and be blameless."
I am Almighty God. You know what he said? He said, "I
am El Shadai." Of course, we've talked about this a lot. You've
heard me teach on this. This means that that I am the
God of all sufficiency in all things. I am the God of
all provision. He didn't say, "I'm the God of Walmart." Now, you
could go to Walmart and you could get a lot of stuff,
right? I mean, you can get a lot of different kind of
a wide variety of stuff at Walmart. But he didn't say, "I'm
the god of Walmart." What he was saying is, "I'm the God
of Walmart, Costco, HB, Kroger, uh, Academy Sports. I'm the God that
has all sufficiency. Anything that you will ever need in this life,
I've got it." >> That's a big announcement right there. >> That is a
huge announcement. If you're ever going to need anything, you have you
don't have to look any place else but to me. >> Man, that
that alone right there ought to be enough for us, right? When
you're in need, when you're struggling with something, he's El Shai. >> You
can go to him and get anything that you need. He's better
than Walmart. >> He's better than Costco, Sam's Club, right? He's better. I
mean, everything that you possibly need. How many you know that uh
I was it's kind of interesting when you watch the World Cup
this year and all the people from other countries, you know, coming
into our country and and seeing how America actually is versus what
the woke news media talks about. And it's interesting to hear all
the comments, right? They're just like, "Wow, this is amazing." And they
were I heard one guy talking about Walmart, how you could you
could go there and get anything, right? They're just amazed at all
the things that we have in America. And what they say is,
"It's not what we thought it was." >> Yeah. because there's so much
provision here. Well, this is nothing compared to El Shadai. >> El Shadai
has everything. So, Abram is hearing this. He said, I'm El Shadai.
Look at verse number two. And I will make my covenant between
me and you and will multiply you exceedingly. Say exceedingly.
You know, God doesn't do anything on a small scale. >> Have you
noticed that nothing that he does is small? >> It's all exceedingly.
>> It's all big. >> He doesn't do things in a small way. He
created a universe so vast and so big we don't even know.
We can't even count. Remember he told he told him he said,
"Go out and count the stars. count the sand on the you
can't even count it this so big that's exceedingly >> that means more
than enough right so God does things in to a great degree
or exceedingly look at verse three then Abram fell on his face
and God talked with him saying as for me you know in
a covenant relationship there are two parts God is saying this is
my part and you know he's about to tell him what his
part is it's a two-way way street. A covenant relationship is not
a one-way street. How many you know a marriage covenant is not
a one-way street. >> It's not your way or the highway. Uh that's
not how a marriage works. >> If you want to have a successful
marriage, it's a two-way street, right? There's two people in this marriage.
It's not just one. So God said, "As for me," he fell
on his face. He said, "As for me, my covenant is with
you, and you shall be a father of many nations." Now, remember,
he couldn't have kids. Remember, he he tried to have a kid
with Hagar and had Ishmael, but he wasn't able to have a
child with Sarah, his wife, or Sarah, his wife. Look at look
what it says here. Verse number five. No longer shall your name
be called Abram, but your name shall be Abraham. And I for
I have made you a father of many nations. So God changed
his name. Some of y'all need a name change. >> Some of y'all
need to know you've had a name change.
>> Some of you need to know it's already happened, but you don't
know about your covenant.
>> So he changed his name. We're going to we're going to dive
a little bit into this today. Changed his name. If we're going
to jump down here in verse number 15, I love this. Then
God said to Abraham, "As for Sarai, your wife, you shall not
call her name Sarai, but Sarah shall be her name, and I
will bless her and also give you a son by her." And
then they will then I will bless her, and she shall be
a mother of nations. Kings of peoples shall come from her. So,
he changed Abram's name to Abraham and he changed Sarah's name to
Sarah. Aren't you glad, ladies, he didn't just do it for the
man? >> Come on, ladies. I know it's not Mother's Day, but you
can say amen to that one. Aren't you glad that what God
is no respector of persons and it's not just a male oriented
Christianity that God will his covenant promises are just as much for
you than it is the man. >> Ladies, >> God is not holding back
on you. >> He wasn't doing things for Abram he wasn't going to
do for Sarah. >> But I want you to notice something. They needed
a name change. They needed a name change. And before Abram and
Sarai could not have kids, they couldn't reproduce. But I what I
want you to see this morning is that Abraham and Sarah can.
>> What I want you to see this morning is Abraham and Sarah
in their covenant can. >> Amen. They got access to something now they
didn't have access to before.
>> Can you see something's happening here? >> Abram and Sarai could not have
a baby, but covenant man Abraham and covenant woman Sarah can.
>> What am I telling you? When you begin to function and operate
in your covenant, there are things that God's going to do in
you and through you that you can't do right now. >> You're not
able to even see it or even do it. This is beyond
what you've ever dreamed. You're like Abram and Sarah, not able to
have a baby, and you've been walking around saying, "We can't have
a baby. We can't have a baby. Oh, wo is me." And
God is saying, "You need to look at your covenant. Amen. >> You
need to know that your name has changed.
>> And not only did he change their names, but did you know
God changed his name, too? >> Did you know that? What did he
what did he announce himself as after this moment? Everywhere after this,
he says, "I'm the God of Abraham. >> I'm the God of Abraham,
of Isaac, of Jacob." Why? Because this was a generational covenant. It
didn't die with Abram or Abraham. It didn't die with him. It
was passed on to I. That's why the circumcision, the sign or
the mark of the covenant was in the reproductive system of the
man because it was a reproductive covenant. It was to go from
generation to generation to generation. And it wasn't going to end with
Abram. >> Amen. >> So God changed his name. He said, "You need a
name change is what you need, Abram. I'm going to change your
name to Abraham. I'm going to change her name to Sarah." So,
what did he do when he changed their names? Let's look at
it here. First, let's I just want to take a look at
God's name. You got that first graphic? Put that up there. This
is God's proper name. Now, we call him God. That's kind of a
general term. And anytime you see God translated in the Old Testaments,
it's typically Elohim or Elohim. I say Elohim. Elohim. But I'm from
Oklahoma, so I could do that. Elohim. Elohim. And that's kind of
God's plural name. That's like saying God. But you know, God has
a specific name. That's like saying, uh, I'm a male. That's kind
of general, right? That's true. I'm a male or I'm a guy
or I'm a boy. And it's it's it's really simple to know
that, right? We know why I'm a boy and why, you know,
it's not confusing, is it? >> Amen. >> But I also have a name.
My name is Chris. Right? That's my specific name. Well, you know,
God has a name. And this is God's name. We we translate
it Jehovah or sometimes it's translated in English Yahweh, but it's only
four letters. In the Hebrew, there are no vows. So God's name,
his proper name, I don't know if you can see that up there.
His proper name is four letters. So the first one here is
the letter we would we would call a Y, but it's actually
y. The second one is hey. The third one is vav. And
the fourth one is hey. So you can see there when you
put y, w or y, and then h again, you can see
where you put in a couple of vowels. It's Yahweh. That's where
we get the ter the the word. That's why we get we
say it in English because in English we got to have some
vows. Can I buy a vow? Right. We had to buy some
vows to put it in there because there's no vows in the
Hebrew. So for it to make sense, we had to put vows
in there. But that's actually God's name right there. So now let's
take a look at Abraham's name. Let's put the Abraham up here.
What do you notice about Abraham's name? There's a letter that was
inserted from Abram to Abraham. And it's, you can see here the
A B R and then M. That was Abram. But there was
a letter that was inserted there. You see the H. One letter.
One letter was changed from Abram to Abraham. And it was the
letter Hey. Now, let's pull up Sarah's. Pull hers up. Same thing
right at the very end of Sarah's name. Sarah doesn't isn't spelled
this way, but Sarah has the letter hey at the end of
it. Why am I pointing this out? Because God's name is Yadhee
vi. So God took a letter part of his name and he
put it in his covenant partner's name. Yeah. >> And he took that
not just for Abram, but he did it for Sarah, too. >> And
he put his name in your name. >> You see that?
>> That's how he changed their name. He put his name in their
name. So, okay, pastor, why is that so significant? Well, we need
to understand some things about Hebrew letters. They're not like English letters.
Hebrew letters themselves have meaning. You know, our letters don't have a
lot of meaning. We don't have some of them do, but most
of them don't. Our our English is weird. I think English is
one of the most challenging languages to learn. I'm still trying to
learn it. My English ain't very good. Because, you know, we say
so many things, right? We we have these phrases and these words
that mean the same. They sound the same, but they're different and
they mean different things. It's just so weird. I can't imagine trying
to learn English. Can you? But the Hebrew language is very different
and unique because letters have meanings. And this letter hey has a
meaning. Do you want to know what the meaning is? Here's the
meaning of the letter hey. It means breath of life. It means
something that's revealed. It means grace.
Grace. God's grace. It means power. It means the spirit.
>> Can you see what God was doing here? >> He didn't just put
He didn't just change his name, right? Well, we know that's a
part of a covenant, right? The the names change. And you see
that in covenant partners all the time. There's always the name change.
We get married and in our culture the the wife changes her
name, right? Takes on the name of a husband. But many cultures,
they share the same name. Put a hyphen in it. And so
God put his his that letter hey from his name into Abram's
name and into Sarah's name. And when he did that, he was
putting his grace there. He was putting his spirit there. He was
putting his power there. >> Amen. >> And Abram
could not have a child. But Abraham with the grace of God,
with the spirit of God can.
Sarah I could not either, but Sarah can. Well, well, pastor, what
does this mean for us? I mean, why? Okay, good for them,
but what does this mean for us? Did you know that you've
been given a name?
>> Did you know that when you were born again, you were given
what happens when you get born again? The spirit of God comes
to live on the inside of you, >> inserted on the inside of
you. You got God's spirit. And not only did you receive the
spirit of God, you received also his grace. >> Did you or did
you not? >> Matter of fact, the Bible says the fullness of the
Godhead bodily. >> You got it all. >> Not just one little aspect. You
got all of him. >> You didn't just get part of God. You
got all of him on the inside of you. So when you
accept Jesus as your personal savior, God does the same thing only
better. >> And then you got a name change. What name did you
get? Some of you are like, I don't know, pastor, but it
sounds good. [laughter] It's not complicated. I'm not trying to trick you.
Let's read about the name you got. Philippians chapter 2 verse number
eight. and being found in appearance as a man, talking about Jesus
now, he humbled himself and became obedient to the point of death,
even the death of the cross. Therefore, God also has highly exalted
him and given him the name which is above every name.
>> What name is above every name? The name of Jesus. Right? that
at the name of Jesus, every knee should bow
>> of those in heaven, of those on earth, and of those under
the earth. Well, that covers a lot of territory, doesn't it? >> And
that every tongue should confess. Why we say a confession every week?
Because God is a confession God. We need to agree with him.
I need to say what he says. That's what a confession is.
Every sh every tongue should confess that Jesus Christ is Lord to
the glory of God the father.
So the name that we have is the name of Jesus. And
it's not just the name, it's the name above every other name.
It's the name that's greater than every other name. It's the name
that's more powerful than any other name. >> And I can tell by
your reactions already, we don't understand our covenants very well. >> Because I
just talked about how Abraham could do things with his name change
that he couldn't do before. Why? Because he received the grace. He
received the spirit of God, the power of God on his life.
And when you got born again, you received the spirit of God.
You receive the grace of God. And you and I have been
given a name. >> And it's not just any old name. Wouldn't that
been funny? I'm Bill. We'll give you a name. Bill. Just a
just a random Bill. Just plain old random. What's What's significant about
that? Nothing. Just I just given you a name. No. This name
has meaning. This name has power. >> This name has authority. Look at
this in Mark chapter 16 verse number 17. It says, "And these
signs will follow those who believe in my name." >> What was he
doing? He's given us his name. >> In my name. What are you
supposed to do? They will cast out demons
in my name. In my name, they will speak with new tongues.
Boy, I tell you what, we've eliminated a lot of the body
of Christ already, haven't we? >> Well, you talking about demonic stuff. I
don't anything to do with that because I'm scared of demons. Why
would you be scared of a demons? You got a new name.
>> Why would any Christian be afraid of the devil >> or a demon?
Why? Tell me why. Because they don't know their covenant. >> And they
don't know they've received a name. >> They don't know it. They're strangers
to the covenants of promise. have no idea of what actually happened
to them when they got born again. Can you see how deceptive
the devil is? He does not want you to know this. >> The
last thing he wants is a bunch of Christians running around this
earth that know their covenant with God. >> That's the last thing he
wants. Christians that don't know their covenant are no problem for him
at all. >> Why? Because they're not going to resist. They're not going
to stand on their covenant promises. They're not going to confess their
covenant promises. They're not going to do anything. They're going to be
afraid of the devil. They're going to be afraid of some kind
of a bug, a stomach bug.
Let me let me say it another way. Stomach parasite.
They'll be afraid of some some virus or some disease. And I
know every I know y'all know what I'm talking about. It's getting
close to home now, isn't it? Shouldn't you be? Well, pastor, we
should be afraid. We should respect these things. Really, my Bible doesn't
say that. My Bible says I've been given a name. >> I got
a name change. I'm no longer Chris Carter. >> When I accepted Jesus
as my savior, I am now Chris Carter in Christ.
[applause] >> You see, God put me in his name.
>> [laughter] >> He put his name in Abram's name. He put you in
his name.
>> Are we getting it? >> He put you in his name. I am
Chris Carter in Christ. It's not just me. We're in covenant together.
I am Chris Carter in Christ. I've been given his name. And
it says the name above every names that that you can cast
out demons in these names. You can speak with tongues. If they
take up serpents and if they drink anything deadly, it will by
no means hurt them. >> I could eat that nasty virus or I
can eat that bacteria or whatever it is, that bug. I could
eat it for breakfast.
I'm not telling you to go eat it for breakfast. I'm just
saying that you could eat See, here's here's where we go. Here's
this is where the rubber meets the road, guys. Do you know
your covenant or not? Yeah. >> Because many times what we will do
is we will do something like that and we'll eat something and
it's like, man, I knew when I was eating that that wasn't
any good. I think I've got food poisoning. And then what do
you expect to happen after that? You start feeling it, right? Everybody
Everybody's experienced that. But what's the Bible say? You can eat something
deadly in your covenant. Well, Chris Carter eats something deadly, it's it's
going to be bad for him. But Chris Carter in Christ, >> I
said Chris Carter in Christ could eat something deadly and I'm not
even affected by it.
>> Doesn't automatically happen though, does it? You got to know this. >> And
not only do you have to know it, you're going to have
to do something about it when you know it. >> What we're finding
out is many many people don't really know it, or if they
kind of know it, they don't really do anything about it. because
they got more faith in a in a bug, a parasite, a
virus. They got more faith in a doctor's report. They got more
trust in in somebody else's word than God's word. >> When God said,
"My covenant I will not break."
>> The Bible says that our covenant that we have is a better
covenant than what they had. >> It's better. That means if if they
couldn't have kids, but now the covenant man, Abraham and Sarah can
have kids. If you're having trouble having children,
>> come on, somebody. >> If you're experiencing the same thing they're experiencing, a
better covenant would not mean you can't either. Well, he did it
for them, but he wouldn't do it for me. You don't know
your covenant. >> You're stranger to the covenant of promise. Have no idea.
It says that we could cast out demons. We could take up
serpents. If they drink anything deadly, it will by no means hurt
them. >> Oh, I love that. They will lay hands on the sick.
Who's going to lay hands on the sick? >> The covenant man. >> The
covenant woman will lay hands on. We're talking about a covenant man.
Not just any old man. A covenant man as someone who knows
their covenant, living in their covenant. We know this from from scripture.
You remember when these guys tried to go out there and cast
a demon out of somebody, seven sons ofKeva, and they tried to
cast a demon out, and the demon thrashed them, >> beat them up,
stripped them naked, bleeding, hurting, and they were trying to do it,
but they didn't have a covenant, >> and they didn't even know anything
about it. They said in the name of Jesus that Paul preaches
about. They weren't in the covenant. They had no idea what this
was. They had no idea how. They just saw Paul doing it.
So they said, "Well, let's go give it a shot. Let's just try.
Let's let's look at exactly how he did it. Let's create a
formula and then let's go over here and repeat the formula and
see if it works." That's not covenant. >> But you know, that's how
a lot of Christians do things. >> Oh, we're bad about that. We
are so bad about that. I'll tell you who's really bad about
it. It's pastors. Churches. Well, what's working for them? Oh, you know what?
They got this and that and they bought these fancy lights. So,
we better get those. Oh, and you know what they do? They get
up here and they don't say, "I'm the lead pastor." They say,
"I'm the lead communicator at Movement Church."
That'll do it. And their church grew by like 10 times, right?
So, let's go do what they've been doing. I've been to many
church uh conferences in my life. And you know, that's a lot
of what they are. >> Here's what we do. Just take this and
go do it at your church. Well, I'm not saying that there's
not things you can learn from other people. I'm not saying there's
not good practices and things like that, but nothing. I said nothing.
I said nothing replaces the leading of the Holy Spirit.
>> And and I got news for you. You ready? You're not the
Holy Spirit.
>> I'm not the Holy Spirit. I got him in me. You've got
him in you. But you're not the Holy Spirit. I'm not led
by you. I'm led by the spirit. >> I'm not led by what
they're doing. I'm not led by what they're doing. But that's exactly
what the seven sons ofKea did. And guess what? We laugh about
that story. They're bleeding and naked. [laughter] How many Christians are bleeding
and naked right now? bleeding, hurting, >> broken, >> no hope,
and they're wondering why. And they they read the Bible all the
way through, but they don't know, >> because they don't know how to
live in their covenant. They don't know the covenant promises, and they
don't know how to activate the covenant promises. Do you know how
Abram did this? Abram, now think about this. God spoke to him
directly. He didn't announce it to everybody. He didn't even announce it
to everybody that was on the earth. He spoke it to him.
>> You're going to be the father of many nations. I'm changing your
name. It's now going to be Abraham. I'm putting my name in
your name. So now think about this. The very first drop out
of the hat, what happens? Abram walks out, goes outside the next day,
and someone says, "Hey, Abram, he's got a choice, doesn't he?" Oh,
here's where the rubber meets the road, isn't it? He's got a
choice. What does he say? Um, no, no, no, no. My name's
not Abram anymore. It's Abraham. >> And Abraham means the father of a
multitude. [laughter] >> So, he just went out there and said, "Don't call
me Abram anymore. Call me Abraham. Call me the father of a
multitude, a father of many." When he had, you know, couldn't have
kids with Sarah. Day after day after day, constantly. Hey,
Abram. I know you don't know yet, >> but let me go ahead
and tell you, I'm not Abram anymore. I'm Abraham. >> You see, I
have a covenant with God. >> He's changed my name. He's given me his
name. I'm now Abraham, the father of many. How many times do
you think Abraham had to do that? >> More than once? >> Probably more
than twice. probably day after day after day, he was probably challenged
with it. How does that relate to us? Well, day after day
after day, you've got people challenging you. You've got the devil challenging
you. Oh, you're never going to be Oh, you're probably going to
catch this. This is going around. Not this covenant guy.
>> Well, this happens to everybody. It's just going around. Everybody's going to
get it. Not this guy.
Not this covenant man. Not this covenant woman. I have a new
name.
[laughter] When you when you yell and say, "Hey, poor boy. Come
here. I'm not coming >> because that's not me. >> Hey sick man, get
over here. I'm not sick. I'm not coming."
You see what I'm saying? When people speak against you and the
covenant that you have, most Christians speak against it themselves. >> And they
call themselves something they're not. >> Well, you know, I'm just old sinner.
No, you're not. >> You were before, but now you're not. Well, you
know, this virus goes around, everybody gets it, and I'll probably It's
just going to go through everybody, and I'm going to get it,
and my brother will get it, my sister will get it, my
kids will get it, my husband will get it, and we'll probably
get it. It'll probably last couple weeks. You know, that's not what
a covenant man says. >> A covenant man says what his covenant partner
said about it, and that no evil shall befall you, nor any
plague go near your dwelling. >> Amen. Remember we just titled Psalms 91.
>> He'll give his angels charge over you. He could eat anything deadly
and it won't hurt you. What if it's demonic? What if it
is? You've got authority. Why? Because you have been given a name.
>> And it's not just any old random name, Bill. It's the name
above every other name. Give me a name.
Give me a name. >> Pete. >> What' you say? Pete. [laughter] >> No, I
mean something.
>> Cancer is a name. >> Heart disease is a name, Pete. Man, I
hope if there's a Pete watching online, I'm sorry
that I didn't say it. Jesus loves you, Pete. Probably short for
Peter. He was a disciple. Amen.
Give me a name. >> There you go.
>> Uh, autoimmune disease. >> I mean, you can just keep going, right? Just
keep going. Keep going and keep going. And when you go to
the doctor and they said, doctor says, "This is what you have."
You need to tell them, "Well, I know you don't understand, doc,
but see I'm in covenant with God. Yes, >> Abram had that, but
Abraham doesn't. >> I've been given a name. >> I got a new name
now. >> That means something. >> That means I don't have to have that.
>> That means I'm no longer not going to have the ability or
the grace to have children. I've been given a name. >> And it's
the name above every other name. >> He has put our name in
his name. >> Yes. I'm Chris Carter in Christ. You know, you need
to see yourself that way. I'm Josh Swink in Christ. It's not
just me anymore. You know, when you get married, it's not just
you anymore. >> Have you figured that one out? >> It's not just you
anymore. You can't just decide on your own. Well, you can, but
you ain't going to be married very long. >> You can't just decide
on your own. You What do you do? You always consult with
your covenant partner. You just you consult with your covenant partner and
you're like, "Yeah, I'd like to go. You want to go out
and eat here? You want to go eat there?" "Nah, I don't
really know what I want to eat." Well, you know what that's
code for. She's got somewhere she wants, but she's just waiting for
you to say it. So, you got to go down the list,
right? Down the list, down, down, down. And then we come into
agreement, right? You don't do things without your covenant partner. How many
Christians are functioning without their covenant partner? Yeah, >> they're they're functioning outside
of their covenant as if they don't even have one. It's like
slapping God in the face. >> And then when God said, "Here's my
promise in the word," we say, "Well, I don't know. I don't know
about that, pastor." Boy, I don't know about that. I don't know.
It's just so hard to trust God. Do you understand what a
covenant is? Do you understand that if God broke his covenant, which
he will not, he said, "My covenant I will not break." But
if he did, the whole universe would be destroyed. Because the whole
universe, the Bible says in Colossians 1, is being held together by
his word.
>> He will not break his covenant. His promises are yes >> and so
be it in my life. >> That's covenant language. >> Abram day after day
after day had to remind people, had to tell people, "No, no,
no, no. Abraham, Abraham, he had a choice. He could have succumbed
and said, "Hey, hey, Abram, come over here." I can just see
him. Act like I didn't hear him. I don't even hear that.
That's like when you you yell, "Bill, come here." I'm not coming.
That's not my name. Abram's not responding to that name. He only
responds to Abraham. I'm talking about how you can live in your
covenant. >> We can follow the father of our faith, Abraham. So
Abraham did not respond to Abram any longer. Why are you responding
to those things? Why are you just accepting those things? That's not
who you are anymore. >> You've been given a name. The name above
every other name. That the name of Jesus, every knee has to
bow. >> I'm in I'm in Christ. I have a covenant with almighty
God. How did I get in my covenant? because he shed his
blood >> and he entered into the holy of holies we talked about
last week in heaven in the temple and offered his own blood
washed my sin away. Ah you old dirty rotten sinner I'm not
a sinner. >> Say hey sinner come here I'm not coming either.
Do you know your covenant? Do you know what belongs to you
in your covenant? Do you know how to live in your covenant?
Do you know the name that you've been given? He changed your
name, too. You are now baptized into Christ and you've been given
a name. I want us to end the service a little bit
different today. I want us to do something a little bit different
because what I really have was impressed by the spirit to do
today is I want us to focus on that name. I want
us to meditate on that name. We're going to sing a song
together. I want everyone to stand with us. Go ahead and stand.
We're going to sing a song together. And at the end of
this song, we're going to make some declarations in the name of
Jesus. Amen. >> Amen.
I could sing in your name [singing] [music] for all my life
and still find [music and singing] what to love these times.
Just [music] be the name ever on [singing] my lips.
[music] Sweeter every time that I call on it. There's just something
about your name. [music and singing] There's just something about your name. There's just
something about your name [singing] that makes me [music] cry. Holding.
There is no other [singing] name.
There is no other name. [singing] There is no other name. [music]
Jesus, you're worthy. [singing]
And you have been the [music] friend to [singing] never
left. I won't [music] forget your faithfulness. [singing]
Jesus be the name [music and singing] ever on my lips.
[music] Sweeter every [singing] time that I call on it. There's just
something [music] about your name. There's just something about your name. [singing]
>> [music] >> There's just something about your name that makes [music and singing] me cry
holy. Oh, there is no other name.
There is no [singing and music] other name.
There is no other name. Jesus, [music] you're [singing] worthy. Something
there's just something about your name. There's something about [music and singing] your name.
There's just something about your name makes me cry [music and singing] holy.
There is no other name.
There is no [music and singing] other name.
There is no other name. Jesus, you're worthy. [music] You are.
[singing] Come on. [music] We lift up the name of Jesus.
The name above every [singing] other name. [music] Oh, we thank you
Lord for power [singing] in your name.
Oh Jesus, [music and singing] your name is like the northern light. The one
the darkness [music and singing] can't deny. The resurrection and the life. [singing] Jesus.
[music] Jesus. Your name can save. Your name can heal. Your name
can make [singing] the storm be [music] still. You never fail. We
never will. Jesus. [music and singing] Jesus. The bread of life
broken for us. The wounded [singing] and the worthy [music] one. The
first, the last is still [singing] to come. Jesus. [music] Jesus the
king. The world overwhelmed [singing] the great. The Lord who [music] will
forever reign. The name [singing] above all other names. Jesus.
[music] [singing] Oh Jesus be the name.
Jesus be the name. Oh Jesus be [music] the name [singing] that
gives all the glory.
Oh Jesus [music] be the name. Oh Jesus be the name. [music]
Jesus be the name that gets all the [singing] glory.
[music] Oh Jesus be the name.
Jesus be the name [singing] of it all. Jesus be [music] the
name that gets all the [singing] glory. [music] Oh Jesus
be the name.
Jesus be [music] the name. be the name. Jesus be the name
that can all thy [music and singing] glory.
Oh,
[music]
[singing] Jesus [music] glory.
Oh, [music]
the name Jesus.
[music and singing] Jesus be the name.
Jesus be the name. Oh [music] Jesus be the name that gets
all [singing] the glory of the glory. Jesus be the name. [music and singing]
Be the name. Be the name. Jesus be the name the name
be the name. [singing] >> Jesus be the name that gets all [music]
the glory.
Oh, [music]
say the name Jesus. [music]
[singing] shout the name Jesus. [music]
[singing] Come on, lift up the name of Jesus. [music] >> Thank you,
Lord. >> Thank you, Jesus. >> The name that's above all names.
that at the name of Jesus, every knee must bow. Cancer
must bow, depression must bow, poverty must bow, >> viruses must
bow at the name of Jesus. >> Thank you, Jesus.
>> Oh, thank you, Lord. >> You get all the glory >> and praise.
Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Jesus. Now, this is what I want
us to do. Every single person here, you're dealing with something. Maybe
it is sickness. Maybe it is a virus. Maybe it's poverty. Maybe
it's been on you for your whole life. Maybe it's anxiety or
fear or depression. Here's what I want you to do. What we're
going to do is we're going to make a confession of faith
>> based on the word of God and our covenant promises and we
are going to declare that whatever that is be gone
>> in the name. Oh, I said in the name. In the name
above every name. Do you believe that? Do you believe that his
name is above every other name? >> Do you believe that in his
name is power, >> authority?
Dominion.
Do you believe you have it? >> All right, let's do it. I'm
going everybody do this together. I'm going to say one, two, three,
and then you declare what that is. You just speak it with
your mouth. If it's anxiety, say anxiety. If it's fear, say fear.
If it's some sort of sickness, you say it. Heart disease, you
say it. Diabetes, you say it. Why? Because I'm talking to it.
Do you know that Jesus talked to stuff that most people wouldn't
talk to? He talked to a tree. He talked to sickness and
disease.
I don't know if that anxiety can hear. Oh, you better believe
it can. I don't know if that cancer can hear. Oh, you
better believe it can. So, we're going to do that. We're going
to we're going to speak that. And I want you to say
what it is. And the Bible says when you believe it in
your heart, you confess that with your mouth. What we're going to
confess is that that thing be gone in the name of Jesus.
All right, y'all ready? One, two, three. Say it. Say it.
be gone from my life in the name above every
name. The name of Jesus.
Thank you Lord. >> Thank you Lord. >> Oh thank you Lord for our
covenant promise our covenant name. Oh thank you Jesus.
>> Oh let's praise him for it now. All that's left is to
praise it. That's all that's left. The work has been done. We
don't have to strive or worry or fret. It's over. >> Oh, thank
you, Lord.
You say, "Pastor, does that mean it's a ceasefire?" No. I'm declaring
it's over.
>> The attack is over. It's done. It's dead. It's been wiped out.
You know, that's what the enemy has to be. You got to
deal with the enemy. There is no negotiation with the devil. There's
no negotiation with cancer, with anxiety or fear. Well, I'm just learning
to cope. Pastor, you need to eradicate that from your life.
>> You need to be just like April. Not this guy. Not anymore.
I'm a covenant man. >> I have a covenant with God. I'm Abraham.
I'm Abraham. I don't care what I used to be. And he
said, now listen to me now. He said it before he had
the promised child.
He said it before he had it. That's what faith does. Faith
declares the end from the beginning. That's what we just did.
We just used our new covenant name, the name above every other
name. Amen. >> That at the name of Jesus, every knee has to
bow. Live your life in your covenant.
Use your new name.
Don't act like a a person without a covenant. Don't act like
you're a stranger to the covenant. It's a promise. Know your covenant.
You read the word of God. You see that promise. You're like,
you know what I mean by that? That's me. He just said
it. He just gave it. That's a promise. It's mine. That's not
who I am anymore. I'm not a fearful person any longer. Stop
saying it. That's be like Abraham saying, "I'm not the father of
many. I'm not the father of many. I'm not the father of
many." He didn't say that. He said, "I'm the father of many."
It's who I am now. I got a covenant name. You have
a covenant name. You got your name changed, too. You are baptized
into Christ. You're in covenant with God. Amen. Father, in the name
of Jesus, oh, the name above every other name. Thank you, Lord,
for our covenant. Thank you, Lord, that we are redeemed. Our freedom
has been purchased and we no longer have to live as people
without a covenant with you. We can live in our covenant. Thank
you, Lord, for what you've done 2,000 years ago. Not even what
this morning, but the work was done 2,000 years ago. I thank
you, Lord, for the revelation today that we got on what you've
already done. the revelation on our new name. And I thank you,
Lord, that we will be a people from this moment on who
will not be considering ourselves as people without a covenant, but we'll
walk in our new covenant and use our new name in the
name of Jesus. Amen. Amen. Praise God. Well, if you guys need
prayer, we got a prayer team up here. Go in the power
and authority in the name of Jesus. You're dismissed. God bless you.
[singing] [music]
[singing] >> Darkness can't [music] deny the resurrection and [singing] the life. Jesus.
Jesus. [music] Your name can save. Your name can heal. Your name
[music and singing] can make the stor. You never fail. You never will.
Jesus, Jesus, [music] the bread of life [singing] broken for us.
The wounded and the worthy [music] one. The first, [singing] the last,
and still to come. Jesus. Jesus. [singing] The king who overwhelmed
[music] the crane. The Lord who will forever. [singing] The name above
all other [music] names. Jesus.
Jesus be [singing] the name. [music] Jesus be the name.
Jesus [music] be the [singing] name that gets all the glory.
[music] Jesus be [singing] the name.
Jesus be the [music] name.
Jesus [singing] be the name that gets all the glory. [music]
Jesus be the name.
Jesus be the name. [music and singing] Jesus be the name that gets
all the glor.
Jesus be the [music] name.
Jesus be the name.
Jesus be the name that gets [music and singing] all the glory.
[singing]
Oh
[singing] [music] Jesus.
[singing] Oh
[singing]
Jesus.
Oh we thank you Lord.
[singing]
>> We love your name. >> Oh we bless we bless your name.
In the name of Jesus.